let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Kabul is the capital of?",
        answer: "Afghanistan",
        options: [
            "Venezuela",
            "Bhutan",
            "Afghanistan",
            "Chile"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Yerevan is the capital of?",
        answer: "Armenia",
        options: [
            "Armenia",
            "China",
            "New Zealand",
            "Libya"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Baku is the capital of?",
        answer: "Azerbaijan",
        options: [
            "Nigeria",
            "Costa Rica",
            "Spain",
            "Azerbaijan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Manama is the capital of?",
        answer: "Bahrain",
        options: [
            "Bahrain",
            "United Kingdom",
            "Serbia",
            "Malta"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Dhaka is the capital of?",
        answer: "Bangladesh",
        options: [
            "Iraq",
            "Japan",
            "Bangladesh",
            "Cyprus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Thimphu is the capital of?",
        answer: "Bhutan",
        options: [
            "Bhutan",
            "Zimbabwe",
            "Ghana",
            "Ukraine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Bandar Seri Begawan is the capital of?",
        answer: "Brunei",
        options: [
            "India",
            "Kazakhstan",
            "Turkey",
            "Brunei"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Phnom Penh is the capital of?",
        answer: "Cambodia",
        options: [
            "Fiji",
            "Cambodia",
            "Jordan",
            "Kuwait"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Beijing is the capital of?",
        answer: "China",
        options: [
            "Malaysia",
            "Singapore",
            "China",
            "Laos"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Nicosia is the capital of?",
        answer: "Cyprus",
        options: [
            "Cyprus",
            "South Korea",
            "Thailand",
            "Myanmar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Tbilisi is the capital of?",
        answer: "Georgia",
        options: [
            "Lebanon",
            "Malaysia",
            "Mongolia",
            "Georgia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "New Delhi is the capital of?",
        answer: "India",
        options: [
            "Malaysia",
            "India",
            "South Korea",
            "Indonesia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Jakarta is the capital of?",
        answer: "Indonesia",
        options: [
            "Malaysia",
            "Greece",
            "Afghanistan",
            "Indonesia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Tehran is the capital of?",
        answer: "Iran",
        options: [
            "Iran",
            "Iraq",
            "Israel",
            "Italy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Baghdad is the capital of?",
        answer: "Iraq",
        options: [
            "Lebanon",
            "Iraq",
            "Georgia",
            "Venezuela"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Jerusalem is the capital of?",
        answer: "Israel",
        options: [
            "Colombia",
            "India",
            "Indonesia",
            "Israel"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Tokyo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Japan",
        options: [
            "North Korea",
            "Thailand",
            "Japan",
            "Maldives"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Amman is the capital of?",
        answer: "Jordan",
        options: [
            "Jordan",
            "Laos",
            "Bahrain",
            "Pakistan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Nur-Sultan / Astana is the capital of?",
        answer: "Kazakhstan",
        options: [
            "Pakistan",
            "Kazakhstan",
            "Afghanistan",
            "Kyrgyzstan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Kuwait City is the capital of?",
        answer: "Kuwait",
        options: [
            "Malaysia",
            "Lebanon",
            "Mongolia",
            "Kuwait"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "Bishkek is the capital of?",
        answer: "Kyrgyzstan",
        options: [
            "Kyrgyzstan",
            "Iran",
            "India",
            "Qatar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Vientiane is the capital of?",
        answer: "Laos",
        options: [
            "Libya",
            "Malaysia",
            "Laos",
            "Turkey"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "Beirut is the capital of?",
        answer: "Lebanon",
        options: [
            "Lebanon",
            "Indonesia",
            "Sri Lanka",
            "Syria"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Kuala Lumpur / Putrajaya is the capital of?",
        answer: "Malaysia",
        options: [
            "Lebanon",
            "Malaysia",
            "Tajikistan",
            "Vietnam"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Male is the capital of?",
        answer: "Maldives",
        options: [
            "Myanmar",
            "Malaysia",
            "Mongolia",
            "Maldives"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "Ulan Bator is the capital of?",
        answer: "Mongolia",
        options: [
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "Mongolia",
            "Iran",
            "India"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "Naypyidaw is the capital of?",
        answer: "Myanmar",
        options: [
            "Turkey",
            "State Of Palestine",
            "Myanmar",
            "Russia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "Kathmandu is the capital of?",
        answer: "Nepal",
        options: [
            "Nepal",
            "Bhutan",
            "Greece",
            "Bulgaria"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "Muscat is the capital of?",
        answer: "Oman",
        options: [
            "Thailand",
            "Spain",
            "Finland",
            "Oman"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "Islamabad is the capital of?",
        answer: "Pakistan",
        options: [
            "Tuvalu",
            "Bangladesh",
            "Pakistan",
            "Micronesia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 31,
        question: "Manila is the capital of?",
        answer: "Philippines",
        options: [
            "Russia",
            "Argentina",
            "Macedonia",
            "Philippines"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 32,
        question: "Doha is the capital of?",
        answer: "Qatar",
        options: [
            "North Korea",
            "Syria",
            "Qatar",
            "China"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 33,
        question: "Riyadh is the capital of?",
        answer: "Saudi Arabia",
        options: [
            "State of Palestine",
            "Sri Lanka",
            "Singapore",
            "Saudi Arabia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 34,
        question: "Singapore is the capital of?",
        answer: "Singapore",
        options: [
            "Lebanon",
            "Singapore",
            "Mongolia",
            "Philippines"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 35,
        question: "Seoul is the capital of?",
        answer: "South Korea",
        options: [
            "South Korea",
            "Turkmenistan",
            "Canada",
            "Uzbekistan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 36,
        question: "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte is the capital of?",
        answer: "Sri Lanka",
        options: [
            "Myanmar",
            "Sri Lanka",
            "Bangladesh",
            "India"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 37,
        question: "Jerusalem is the capital of?",
        answer: "State of Palestine",
        options: [
            "Yemen",
            "New Zealand",
            "Russia",
            "State of Palestine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 38,
        question: "Damascus is the capital of?",
        answer: "Syria",
        options: [
            "Libya",
            "Syria",
            "Madagascar",
            "Philippines"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 39,
        question: "Dushanbe is the capital of?",
        answer: "Tajikistan",
        options: [
            "Tajikistan",
            "Bhutan",
            "Nepal",
            "Cuba"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 40,
        question: "Bangkok is the capital of?",
        answer: "Thailand",
        options: [
            "Peru",
            "Fiji",
            "Thailand",
            "Iran"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 41,
        question: "Ankara is the capital of?",
        answer: "Turkey",
        options: [
            "Turkey",
            "Russia",
            "Greece",
            "Nigeria"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 42,
        question: "Ashgabat is the capital of?",
        answer: "Turkmenistan",
        options: [
            "Maldives",
            "Malaysia",
            "El Salvador",
            "Turkmenistan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 43,
        question: "Abu Dhabi is the capital of?",
        answer: "United Arab Emirates",
        options: [
            "North Korea",
            "Thailand",
            "United Arab Emirates",
            "Saudi Arabia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 44,
        question: "Tashkent is the capital of?",
        answer: "Uzbekistan",
        options: [
            "Uzbekistan",
            "Uruguay",
            "Uganda",
            "Ukraine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 45,
        question: "Hanoi is the capital of?",
        answer: "Vietnam",
        options: [
            "Andorra",
            "Algeria",
            "Egypt",
            "Vietnam"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 46,
        question: "San’a is the capital of?",
        answer: "Yemen",
        options: [
            "Panama",
            "Costa Rica",
            "Yemen",
            "Jamaica"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 47,
        question: "Pyongyang is the capital of?",
        answer: "North Korea",
        options: [
            "North Korea",
            "Nauru",
            "Paraguay",
            "Tonga"
        ]
    },
];